Mighty glad to meet you, Mr. Johnson.
- Mr. Johnson.
- Back here.
This is the guy I was telling you about,
my friend from Texas.
Yeah.
- Howard, get him an application.
- Sure.
Sit anywhere you like.
- You said I already had the job.
- It's just a formality.
- You want some coffee?
- Sure.
- Black, right?
- Right.
Jim, I don't need to tell you
how dangerous it is out there.
The guy has a fucked-up leg.
If you were me, would you hire him?
Give the guy a break.
He drove 1,200 miles.
He's too big a risk.
I'll lose my insurance.
Michael, wait.
Mike, why did you tell him about your leg?
He'd have found out sooner or later.
So what? By then you'd have had the job.
That wouldn't be right.
Shit.
I'm really sorry about this.
Don't worry about it, Jim.
It's not your fault.
Now what will you do?
I don't know. Maybe I'll rob a bank.
- You need some money?
- That's okay.
- I'll spot you a couple bucks.
- Don't worry about me.
I'll be all right.
You stay in touch.
Yeah. You too.
Anybody here?
Is anybody here?
Hello.
I said, is anybody here?
- Can I help you?
- I need some gas.
- Fill her up?
- No, just five dollars' worth.
Texas, huh?
What in the devil brings you
out here to Wyoming?
- I'm looking for work.
- What kind of work are you looking for?
I hoped to get on a drilling crew.
Roughneck, huh?
Why don't you try Red Rock?
About 50 miles down the road.
There's a bar there called The Red Rock.
Most of the local crew hangs out there.
Hell, maybe somebody there
can head you in the right direction.
Mighty fine old car you got here.
You know, they just don't
make them that way anymore.
That will be five dollars.
Five it is.
Thank you.
- You open?
- Yeah.
- Got any coffee?
Thanks.
You were supposed to be here last Friday.
I was beginning to think
I'd have to find somebody else.
You are here for the job, aren't you?
- You must be Wayne?
- Yes.
And you're Lyle from Dallas?
- Right.
- Good.
Now just take your coffee
and let's go in the office.
There's the five like we agreed.
I'll have the other five
ready for you when it's...
when it's done.
Today is Tuesday, so she'll be
out riding most of the day.
The best way to do this is
to make it look like a simple burglary.
Just go out to the house...
break in...
and...
mess the place up a little.
Not too much. Just enough.
And...
And then when she comes in, you...
You know what to do.
Thanks.
I figure the cops will spend
a couple months looking for clues.
Once they come up empty-handed,
they'll get frustrated...
and, eventually...
they'll try to blame some drifter
passing through town.
- It happens all the time, you know?
- Yeah.
Who is she?
She's my wife.
Your name Suzanne?
You're married to Wayne, right?
I don't know how to tell you this,
but your husband, Wayne...
he plans to have you murdered.
Is this a joke?
I'm afraid not.
He paid me to do it.
- What will you do?
- I don't know.
I hate to see an innocent woman
get hurt...
but it's an awful lot of money.
Can I fix you a drink?
You're taking this a lot better
than I thought you would.
Have you ever been married?
- What?
- What's your name?
Lyle.
Have you ever been married, Lyle?
It does strange things to people.
Suppose I double his offer,
and you do something for me?
What?
Take care of Wayne.
- Is that all?
- That will do it.
How much gas you have?
Twenty-nine dollars.
119.78.
- You got anything smaller?
- Not today.
Hello?
Hang in there, buddy.
I'll get you out of here.
- Get a doctor!
- What happened?
- Somebody get a fucking doctor!
- Wait here, sir.
Dr. Smoot. ER, stat.
- What happened?
- I hit him with my car.
- Bobby! When?
- About 20 minutes ago.
- Weak pulse. Get him into the ER.
- Right away.
Wait here. I'll need
to ask you some questions.
This way, sir.
Are you finished yet?
No. Have you heard anything?
Sorry. You'll have to wait for the doctor.
Wait.
I was going to move my car.
How's he doing?
It's good you brought him in when you did.
He lost a lot of blood.
Hi, Doc. Is this the guy
that brought him in?
Yeah. Matt, can I talk to you?
- Going somewhere?
- Yeah, my car is out there.
It's in the red zone. I was gonna move it.
- Yeah?
- That was the sheriff.
He's on his way over.
- Did you call him?
- What do you think?
- You got some ID on you?
- Yeah.
Is there a problem, Officer?
Yeah.
Looks like we have
an attempted homicide on our hands.
What are you talking about?
It was an accident.
Then how do you explain these?
He's been shot twice in the stomach.
How is Kurt doing?
He's pretty bad off,
but the doctor says he'll make it.
If there's any change in his condition,
let me know.
"Michael Williams."
You'll be spending some time with us...
until we can get to the bottom of this.
Wayne, can I talk to you for a minute?
You're gonna hold this guy?
- You got somebody else?
- No, but it doesn't make sense...
he'd shoot him,
then bring him to the hospital.
Yeah. Well, Odessa, Texas.
That's not too far.
We can just get him on the phone
if we have any questions.
You and Russ impound the car.
I'll take him to the station.
Yes, sir.
Get in.
All right, kid.
Start talking. You have two minutes
to tell me what is going on.
I thought you needed a stupid bartender.
- Don't fuck with me.
- I'm not.
- Who else knows about this?
- Nobody.
I said, don't fuck with me!
I'm not.
What about the guy in the hospital?
What happened?
I don't know anything about that.
You don't have to worry.
I won't say anything to anyone.
- What about the money?
- It's in my car glove compartment.
Good.
So, what do you think?
Why don't you just drop me off...
and we'll both forget the whole thing.
What the fuck are you doing?
- My car broke down.
- Where? I don't see a car.
- It's just over that ridge.
- Over that ridge, huh?
You're one lucky son of a bitch.
If I hadn't just had my brakes done...
I'd be picking your brains
out of my radiator.
- Fuck.
- Listen, I hate to ask you this...
but could you give me a ride?
I don't know. Are you dangerous?
I just need a ride. You can drop me off
at the nearest gas station.
Okay, cowboy, you got yourself a ride.
Get in.
Son of a bitch.
You banged it up pretty good.
How'd you do that?
- I was in the Marine Corp.
- No shit?
First Forest Recon.
Last unit to leave Vietnam. April of '71.
I got the same one right here.
Where were you stationed?
I was with the 24th in Lebanon.
The truck bomb thing... You were there?
Yeah.
Holy shit! Were you
in that building they hit?
Damn! You are one lucky son of a bitch.
I know!
I mean, I know I'm lucky.
241 guys weren't.
- Thanks for the ride.
- Anytime, soldier.
Are you going in here?
Yeah, I got to take care
of some business...
and I want to buy you a drink.
Thanks, but I should get going.
I nearly greased your can back there.
Now, the least I can do is buy you a beer.
Thanks, but I should get my car.
I'll tell you what.
Let me buy you a beer,
and then I'll help you get your car.
That's okay. You've done enough already.
Now I said I'd help you get your car.
Really, it's okay.
You don't want to drink with me?
I'm not good enough to buy you a beer?
No, it's not that.
Then what the fuck's your problem?
Us Marines got to stick together.
Come on!
- Okay, soldier. I can get my car later.
- That's it.
Now, that's more like it.
All right. Come on.
What'll you have?
I'd like a shot of Jim Beam
and a bottle of Bud.
- How about you?
- The same.
You know,
that never should have happened...
what happened to you
and our boys over there in Lebanon.
You get in there,
you just gotta give it your best shot.
Right.
That will be 6.50.
You got a guy here named Wayne?
- You mean the owner?
- Yeah, that's him.
Wayne Brown.
- Sorry, he's out.
- Damn.
He's probably out looking for me.
I was supposed to be here last week.
I can call him...
if it's important.
Would you? I'd appreciate that.
Tell him Lyle from Dallas
finally showed up.
- He'll know who you mean.
- Sure thing.
I never did catch your name.
- It's nice meeting you, Michael.
- Likewise.
Listen, I have to use the head.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, well, don't piss on the seat,
even if they did.
It's not lucky.
Did you just pick somebody up
outside of town?
- Yeah, I did.
- Where is he?
Now, Wayne, why would you be inquiring?
You check out back that way.
I'll go over here.
He can't have gotten too far.
I'm not going to Sheridan to see a bitch
with a pissed-off husband.
- I can't get to Sheridan till next week.
- Twenty bucks.
I'll tell you something.
The first sign of bullshit...
Give me the goddamn suitcase.
God!
Does that tickle?
'Cause it won't if I pull the trigger.
What the hell are you doing on my truck?
Sorry, boss. I didn't mean to scare you.
Hey, do I look scared to you?
I was trying to ditch my old lady.
You were what?
She caught me in the bar,
and I wasn't supposed to be there.
- She started sprouting horns and shit.
- Bullshit.
Look at that uncontrolled
response to bullshit.
- I hate when that happens.
- Yeah, I don't like it either...
but I had to get out of there.
- So you climbed up on my truck?
- Yeah.
Isn't that kind of stupid?
Yeah, it is, but you've never met my wife.
- She's spooky.
- Yeah?
You're lying to me. Get off my truck.
Come on, get off the truck.
Oh, man.
- I'm headed north if you want a ride.
- Thanks.
There's a ranch just up the road.
You can drop me off there.
What's the deal? Am I taking you
back to or away from your old lady?
Neither. Actually, I have
a little business to take care of.
Business?
Is she pretty?
Yeah, she is pretty.
Good luck, Spider-Man.
Thanks for the ride.
It's okay. It's all right.
I'm not who you think I am.
I lied.
I needed a job real bad.
Your husband offered me one,
and I took it before I knew what it was.
- You're not a killer.
- That's right.
But the guy I'm supposed to be
just drove into town.
- You have to get out of here.
- Suddenly my life's in danger again?
That's right.
You expect me to believe you?
What is this? You want my money?
I don't have any more money.
Get the fuck out of my house!
You're not listening to me.
Your friend, the ranch hand,
has been shot!
- You mean Kurt?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
He was lying in the road,
and I took him to the hospital.
Pack your bags and get going.
- Is he alive?
- Yeah.
- They know who shot him?
- No, he was unconscious.
I wouldn't be surprised if your husband
had something to do with it, would you?
Get dressed.
He's in the living room.
Now go to the balcony.
Come on.
- Is that him?
- Yeah.
- What should I do?
- If I were you, I'd get a divorce.
- Where you going?
- I don't want to be here...
when Lyle from Dallas wakes up, do you?
There's a jeep behind the barn.
Let me grab a coat. I'll be right out.
The fucking story of my life.
- What kind of mileage does this get?
- Why?
We're almost out of gas.
- Which way is the nearest town?
- Medicine Bow is 40 miles that way.
- Is there a sheriff there?
- Yes.
Are you going to the police?
Yeah, I want to get this mess cleaned
before anyone else gets hurt.
What will you tell them?
The truth.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah, I'm sure about that.
How will you explain
impersonating a hired killer...
and taking $10,000
from my husband, the sheriff?
What do you suggest?
I suggest we get as far away from here
as possible.
- You're just gonna leave?
- Yeah.
What the hell do I have
that's worth coming back for?
Russ, give me the registration.
- Son of a bitch got away.
- What?
Yeah, he kicked me. He went berserk.
Want us to call in an APB?
An APB? No, please.
Let's just keep this amongst ourselves.
It's bad enough.
- Did you find anything?
- No, we just started looking.
- Look, find him. Tonight.
- Sure.
- I'll be in the bar.
- You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. Sure. Thanks.
What you got?
Do you suppose this has anything
to do with anything?
- Do you have that money I gave you?
- No, it was in my car.
Wayne's deputies must have it by now.
- How are you paying for the gas?
- I have about 80 bucks left.
Great. Can I see your wallet?
I like that better than Lyle.
- Where are you going?
- I'm thirsty.
I'll be in the bar.
- We should get going.
- You should relax and have a drink.
You wanted to get out of here.
What's one drink?
- What will you have?
- Give me a beer.
You know...
I realize you didn't
have to come back for me.
You could have just left...
but you didn't...
did you?
Thank you.
That will be $1.25.
You must think I'm pretty awful.
- Why is that?
- I did ask you to take care of Wayne.
Right.
Under the circumstances,
I can't say as I blame you.
You're a nice guy, aren't you?
I try to be.
God, I love tequila.
Maybe that's what we should do:
go to Mexico.
- Ever been there?
- Yeah.
- What's it like?
- Hot.
Sounds perfect.
- Let me ask you something.
- Sure.
Why did Wayne try to...
- Get rid of me?
- Yeah.
I'll have another shot.
- Tequila?
- Whiskey.
- You got it.
- Thanks.
It's all about money.
My parents died several years ago
in an accident...
and I received a fairly large
insurance settlement.
Wayne's just gotten used to spending it.
He probably figures
if he divorced me he'd get nothing.
If I'm six feet under the ground
with a bullet in my head...
he gets to keep everything.
- That's hard to imagine.
- That's my husband.
- Hello.
- Wayne, she got away.
The cowboy was here.
They got the jump on me.
- Do you know where they went?
- Hell, no. How could I?
I've been staring at my eyelids
for the last hour and a half.
You can't let them get away.
I didn't come all the way up here
to play hide-and-geek.
You have got to find her.
I'll take a look around,
but it's going to cost you.
- I want another five up front.
- Fine.
Just find her.
When do I get the money?
Tomorrow morning.
Just come to my office.
It's right behind the bar.
- What time?
- 9:30.
I'll be there.
What do you say?
You want to go to Mexico with me or what?
In our present condition,
I don't think we'd get far.
What do you think we should do?
Get a cup of coffee.
I got a better idea.
What's that?
Comfort Inn.
You want to fix me a drink?
Whiskey okay?
Sounds nice.
Don't you like me?
Yeah, I like you.
Then what's the matter?
Just try to make a point
of staying away from married women.
Why? Marriage is just a state of mind.
Not in Texas.
We're not in Texas.
Tell me about Mexico.
Please.
Mexico.
When I was a kid,
my dad took me to Veracruz...
and he bought me a purple sombrero...
and a little guitar.
It was nice.
I'll bet you were a cute little boy.
I don't know.
- We could go there together.
- Yeah?
Get a little house by the ocean.
Drink margaritas all day.
Watch the sun set.
And take siestas together.
Morning, noon and night.
You're up early.
- I've been thinking.
- About what?
About Mexico.
We'll need more than 80 bucks
to get there.
- We're going to Mexico?
- Yeah.
Wayne always keeps some cash
in a safe at the office.
Wait a minute.
You want to go back to Red Rock?
You have a better idea?
You're just gonna walk into your
husband's bar and take his money?
It's my money.
Your money.
You really think
you can get away with that?
I can't let him have it all.
How much money
are you talking about anyway?
Enough. Are you coming?
Okay, I'll...
I'll go.
You sure you have the right combination?
Yes.
- Could he have changed it?
- It's possible. Would you like to try?
Right to 24.
Left to 87.
Right to 56.
Left to 12.
Right to 99.
- That's it?
- Yeah. Let's go.
I can't believe it.
Oh, yeah.
Come in. The door's open.
Good morning, Wayne.
Good morning, fellas.
- What are you boys doing?
- I got a call from the hospital.
One of the nurses was going through
Kurt's clothing. She found this.
How's he doing?
He's in critical condition,
but the doctor says he'll make it.
- Talked to him?
- No. He's under heavy sedation.
I called the FBI. They're on their way.
$1.9 million.
Gotta hand it to you, Wayne.
Or should I call you Kevin?
It's a lot of cash to walk away with.
- Russ, you got that letter?
- Uh-huh.
Came in the mail this morning.
"Sheriff of Red Rock,
Wayne Brown may have hired...
a killer to murder his wife.
She is likely to do the same.
This is not a joke."
This is a joke. What's going on?
I don't know. Why don't you tell me?
Did you pay that guy from Texas
to murder Suzanne?
This is ridiculous.
Was Kurt trying to blackmail you?
- What?
- Is that why you shot him?
Did you guys come here to arrest me?
Kind of looks that way.
Then go ahead. Arrest me.
I have nothing more to say
until I talk to my lawyer.
Okay, let's go.
"Wanted for the theft of $1.9 million...
from the Benton/Barne Steel Mill.
Kevin and Ann McCord.
May be armed and dangerous."
Looks like the only thing
you didn't lie about is your marriage.
It's not what you think. I can explain.
It was Wayne. I had nothing to do with it.
One day he comes home
and says, "Pack your bags."
The next thing I know,
I'm on the FBI's most-wanted list.
What am I supposed to do? He's my husband.
I was in love with him.
There's supposed to be
a half million dollars in that safe.
He must have moved it.
We can find it.
We can be together. We can go to Mexico.
Fuck Mexico!
Michael, please...
don't leave me.
We can be together.
Miss Suzanne...
you're as pretty as advertised.
You look pretty near good enough to eat.
That looks like my gun.
Afternoon, Mike.
Did you have a nice nap?
Did you know that these two...
were a couple of fucking crooks?
Yeah. Suzy here says...
that Wayne was a bookkeeper
in a steel mill in Illinois...
and he figured out how to walk out
of that plant with $2 million.
And she says...
there's half a million
laying around somewhere...
but that Wayner is the only one
that knows where it is.
Now, is that true?
That's what she told me.
If that's the case...
why don't we all go pay Wayner
a little visit...
and see if Suzy's story checks out, okay?
But he's in jail.
Not for long, sweetie pie.
Come on. Get up.
Okay, kids, don't you go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
I'm really sorry.
You were right.
We shouldn't have come back here.
Let's put a cap on the horseshit
and figure a way out of this.
Okay?
- Can you get your hands free?
- No.
The cord's so tight, my hands are numb.
Just keep moving them.
- Do you still have my car keys?
- I think so. Why?
There's a pocketknife on the key chain.
Well, well, now.
Sheriff's office.
Where?
Yeah, we'll be right there.
Matt, that was Bob Finney.
He said the old Duncan place is on fire.
Call the volunteers.
I'll get Russ on the radio.
- You want me to go?
- No, you stay put.
I'll call you if I need you.
Jeff, it's Ted.
The old Duncan place is on fire,
and we need the volunteers to go there.
Hurry. All right. Bye.
Grady, it's Ted.
Listen. The old Duncan place is on fire.
Yeah, we need some help.
Yeah?
- I'll be right with you.
- Yeah.
Everyone else is already on the way.
Yeah, I'm sure.
All right. Okay.
Bye.
Can I help you?
Jesus!
- What happened?
- Nobody knows.
- Anybody inside?
- No.
Wind's not too bad.
We should have this out in no time.
- Does anybody know how it started?
- Not that I know about.
It's turkey. It's one of my favorites.
You're in possession of half
a million dollars. Is that right?
Here's the deal.
You can stay here
and go back to Illinois...
or I can get you out of here now
in exchange for half of that money.
What's it gonna be?
- All right.
- Half the money, right?
Right.
Just get me out.
Come in, Ted.
Pick up if you read me.
You stay by your radio.
I'm going back to the office.
- You put these on.
- What for?
It's part of the deal.
Come on. We don't got all day.
Take it or leave it.
What is this?
Think you're John Wayne?
Put her back in the car.
You take Wayne. I'll get Lyle.
You drive.
Smart cop.
Keep it on the road.
God.
Yeah!
Come on!
All right!
Nice driving! Way to go.
Feels good, don't it?
That old V8 just purrs like a cat.
Yeah.
How does it feel?
Happy couple back together again.
You two got enough legroom?
Where's the money?
Stay on this road.
I'll tell you when to turn.
Okay, boss.
I just want to ask you one thing.
- How did you ever get to be sheriff?
- I was elected.
No shit. How did you rig that?
It wasn't hard. He bought
every voter in the county a drink.
No shit?
Damn. Maybe I ought to do that.
Run for sheriff.
Buy a bar.
What do you think?
- You want a drink?
- No, thanks.
Scotch ain't good enough?
I knew a guy like you once.
Thought he was better than everybody else.
That's it, ain't it?
You think you're better than me,
don't you?
Why don't you just blow me?
You think you are real hot shit,
don't you?
Cowboy, who's got the gun?
You keep your foot on the gas.
Choose life.
Are we having a good time yet?
Forget all these buttons up here.
Just push that down to talk
and let go to listen.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Good. Don't worry. Len's on his way.
Remember, don't touch anything here
until I get back.
- Okay.
- And, Jane, thanks.
- What happened?
- I don't know. I just missed them.
Come on.
HP is sending backup
from Rawlins and Laramie.
- You take 487 East. I'll go west.
- What are we looking for?
A black Buick with Texas plates.
- Now turn off your lights.
- What?
Just turn off your lights
and make that next right up there.
What are we doing?
See this house here?
It belongs to the caretaker.
I don't want him to know we're here.
What is this?
This is the last place
anybody would think to look.
Not bad, Wayner.
- You got a shovel?
- In the trunk.
- When do I get these cuffs off?
- When I get the money.
Come on, Mike. Time for some exercise.
- Where you gonna dig?
- What do you mean?
It's a big graveyard.
What are you saying, Wayne?
Take these cuffs off and I'll point you
in the right direction.
I've been working on the railroad
All the livelong day
Can't you dig any faster?
You're probably thinking to yourself...
"How did I end up out here
with this bunch of losers?"
Right? I'll tell you how.
'Cause you're a thief.
You wouldn't be here
if you weren't, right?
What do you want to do with these two?
- We'll let them go.
- Are you sure about that?
There's no point
in killing them now, is there?
I don't know. I don't like loose ends.
I hope you remember the combinations.
Yeah, I do.
But I won't open that box
till you get rid of the gun.
- You don't trust me?
- Yeah, I trust you.
But, like you said, we're partners.
You have a gun. I don't.
That's my deal. Take it or leave it.
What's to keep me from just shooting
the locks off this box?
Or better yet, I shoot you...
and throw the box in the trunk.
You could do that,
but what about the caretaker?
He might hear the shot.
He might call the deputies.
Might get a little messy, even for you.
You know, I think you got me all wrong.
I'm not greedy.
Fair is fair. Right, partner?
Right.
All right.
There you go.
Open the box.
Wayne, you're making a mistake.
You really think
he'll let you keep half that money?
Mike, that hurt.
Don't worry about me.
I think he'll let me keep it all.
Does this mean that we ain't partners?
Just get away from the car.
Come on.
Move it.
All right.
Get over there.
Move back.
Come on. You aren't
leaving me out here, are you?
After all I've done for you.
I got you out of jail and everything.
I'll tell you. Human nature.
- Who's got the keys?
- I got them right here, partner.
Give them to me.
I'll drive. You just tell me...
Stop moving!
Just slow down, you son of a bitch!
Stay right there!
Now give me the fucking keys!
- Hey, I was just kidding.
- Stop moving!
Give me the keys. Come on.
Okay, now. Easy does it.
Sounded like a gun.
- Let me help you.
- Stay away.
- It's okay.
- No.
Give me the gun.
It's okay.
Better call the sheriff.
Where are the keys?
Where the fuck are the keys?
What the fuck did you do with the keys?
All right. I'll let him know.
Thanks.
Hello, Matt?
Come in, Matt.
Go ahead, Jane.
Mrs. Hortijaye just called,
out at the cemetery.
She said there's people out there
shooting guns.
What should I do?
Tell them to stay put.
We'll be right there.
Come back here.
I'm not finished with you.
You know what?
I am better than you.
The train.
Hurry!
Drop the bag!
Then give it to me!
I guess this means you're going
to Mexico by yourself.
There's the door. I suggest you use it.
Is that what you said to the ranch hand?
- You shot him, didn't you?
- Yeah.
Obviously, I didn't do a very good job.
Next time, I'll be more thorough.
- Why?
- He found out about me.
He wanted my money.
That's what it's all about, isn't it?
Stay away from the bag.
I kind of like you.
Don't make me shoot you.
That's right.
No bullets.
Michael, please,
we can work something out.
There's enough money for both of us.
I'm really sorry.
I'll give you half.
You stupid son of a bitch!
You want it?
Go get it.
You son of a bitch!
Shit.
Adios, Red Rock.